I'll keep going for Rick, for you
James from Tenerife, takes dollars,
human dictionary for 0 dollars, straight Jr.
Ricket, yesterday on ferry, Suns Grant
internet, roots of emptiness,
endless proofs of emptiness, recently a
student approached Newey, don't
tell him I'm not quitting, I'm
leaving this group, thank you, and I said why, he
said it's very difficult and no
[Music]
it's time, he said we should use our
hearts more, do everything from the heart, it's
easier, but Nin said Martin Cortes, you don't
need these assignments and courses, and
Stewart, a spiritual gesture, woman,
only millionaire, speak from the
heart, open your heart, Ordes table,
blabla tractor, tractor schools and
schools,
all this from schools and
main schools without honors, and estimate that it's
too sad, opinion, just open your
heart, director, to care and change,
and yeah, yeah, yeah, they left, they haven't returned
yet,
Durex, in one, said Rifai for Rick,
battle for Wang Gang,
when, just like
in the dictionary, Manu World
and One Point and One Note,
um
life and work in, where they found
Wang Ming, Wang Yong Min, 2 student word
expression, those students who are
special, two  They study, they played,
those students who have a
high spiritual intelligence have already
given that I'm not talking about
normal ones like you, Spears,
sorry, I'm not talking about
normal intelligence, I'm talking about
spiritual intelligence,
Anna Tonna, I'm talking about a
school intelligence where you
can do all the
math problems correctly, and Kings
Wing Simon attack and a log, Demi Moore,
I'm talking about when someone
attacks you, you love them even more, Shanghai
Spears online, that's still a
high spiritual intelligence, you are
in the Buddha said 2 River High spiritual
cool people,
Buddha said those people who have this
strange kind of spiritual intelligence,
Google Labs, love and tact, that they would call
more of a person when this person
attacked them, 2 people and health for more
information about empires, those people
are hungry to have more
information about the emptiness of Disney,
Demi Moore, Graceland, and if you feel when you don't see it, you see that they are going to tell you,
give me more,
Gisela, that there is no lower school,
lower,
Karanka Enigma, nor do I
have any more money,
don't make me, we
will have to sell
[Skate Music]
and clear capabilities
for $100
back for $100
because of wandering and sharing and I want
a precise answer, not an answer
that turns things around. There's no reason why
there are these types of
people with high spiritual intelligence.
Wire the hard way for more
information about the entity because they are
hungry for more information about the emptiness.
Why the water is at risk in our Kings
County and food. Why they want to know
and in school because they want to know about the
highest school, number 2,
number 3, all the schools. By Martin
H's team.
And they already know what's going to happen to their Buddhist group
and they're not going to stop.
That was a precise answer
because they care and love everyone
because the world and day care and day
of war III and IV and they want to help everyone. And want
to help, but they were going to learn to
have all the necessary strategies
to be able to help everyone. The one to
learn and have all the possible
strategies to help the bravery.
[Music]
Perfect answer
In their life, it keeps. Give me time. This
answer is so good that I'm going to give you
an extra one.
[Applause]
[Music]
and I say they drag you live art
if you go to some restaurant like
Inés's restaurant, or go to the excellent
restaurant Twitter
Waters, and if the waiter gives you
especially good service and I throw you tip them, right?
Inside they are excellent servers, that
response was such excellent service,
destructive habitability, that I gave him 100
dollars, gay with, okay, well, but think,
perfect response from Saturday, ones to a
big two, that he, Bodhisattva, wants a
bigger toolbox here,
the commercial, when the plumber arrives at
your house,
well, my plumber this time
is the best I've seen, he almost did a
wildlife fast because he's an old hippie,
I don't know why, he comes and well, like,
long hair and air
conditioning, to the maximum,
I don't know why, I feel like a
relationship with him, he's
been
doing plumbing for 50 years,
his dad was a promoter at Monitor too,
and when you talk to him and he sounds like a
turtle in Uruguay, he's one of
the few people  with whom I talk who does
n't know who I am, we can share and the
poor's intra, we see each other often, so we
can actually sit on the
porch and talk about plumbing,
I'm about wasit urban wanting, he just
wants to talk about one thing, instructing his
troop, his trucks, there's no need,
and the acting, tubes, forfait, and he's been
collecting tools for 50
years,
achievements seen in one track, his truck
appears as a grocery store, in
one, inside a truck, they cause earthquake
boxes, west trains tools, thousands of boxes
with rare tools, in R&B break,
unbranded, and whenever something
breaks down in my house,
Chicken Six, you can
fix it without having to go to the store,
and Casillas and Iniesta, because he has
any piece, no matter how rare, there
in his, also in the classroom, they acquire, and
I'm not kidding, tennis outside
and stronger than Tim Weber, for example,
10 years ago they put a special kind
of filter for the water in my kitchen,
efe starling shelf, and if it starts
banging or there's a pick, I call him and open
sector, opens the  door is overwhelming already so
if I have it
and he has it in his truck
hundreds of filters writes it nobody and it's not
very nice to meet him
even saint even virgin something else very
good about him why I decided to watch this
is very strange and Boksic Saint he
fixes something in Djibouti and my garden
fiction next in teacher and teaches me how to
fix it myself for the next
game over women secret and passes me all
the secrets of plumbing finally
free suggestive so his answer
accepts mypes man that's talking about my
river plumber for scamming the true Sardinian body
of a glove no one hand in
your one
Charles in Cruz Aventín is want to know a
hundred or a thousand different tests of
emptiness picas measurement wherever they
are depend on Grand Stand of
Turespaña because maybe a
student doesn't understand the pen but
understands the two spouses measurement have been
donating extender also intends to
extend measurement mythical Kane
some student doesn't understand the two
spouses but understand the elephant and the
cocaine that this is for Bing to the
vines then the fact of having been
here for the last few days  It rains on
the wall and they already have a good truck,
okay,
show in index, it's Watson, layer, they are layers, so
in this school, the school
of layer, week, lacw, new roots of
emptiness, we collect new evidence
of lay emptiness,
like a good plumber, show and 7 tv, so
I think I feel I have to
tell you five
inés in one in line, final, that I'm going to have to
give you five pieces of evidence of
emptiness in half an hour, Wordsworth, 5
new tools, okay, I say there we go,
that aspect, I live where I live, Tic Tac
dancing, Inditex, I think we're only going to be
able to talk about one of them in
detail,
mens tories, because due to the
person's stories, that is to
say,
this is task number 8,
and it is that divide name set of Firefox, I'm just
going to give you the names of the
five pieces of evidence, in interdiction mode,
we announce that I arrive, little island with final, and
then we're going to go into detail, just
one for half an hour,
and if Twitter cultural thinks of you,
things are empty
and everything in the universe is employment is
empty, Picas M
Ehlers slider  One thing, Martin's love,
because everything in the universe is either one thing
or more than one thing. I'll say it
again, but they have the level. Everything in the
universe is in you. It's vital emptiness
because Erviti Nieves. Everything in the universe,
insider, one time is either one thing or bites.
I keep more than one thing here, like, they are
time, like for example, I'm not a
glove, it's one thing here, sir, and it is, and
your ears acting are two things that I
tell you - before your nose is one thing and
being very mindful, and your ears are more
than one thing. I'm of being.
If you check all the things in the
universe, and there are one thing or one of
two,
that's how you have to do it when you teach
your students. It emits everything indigenous in
the universe. I see the one team is one
thing
[Music]
like everything is one thing or more than one
thing that destroys. There are two here. There are
Sainz, number 2. Take
it out. Proof of Dimes, proof number 2
of emptiness.
The father of the North Middle Scrum is rich.
They are active even in Tunisia,
and by the way, the lower part of the
Middle Way is a very rich source of  tests
for emptiness dry up and event in is so
the second type of
emptiness
is called like diamond chips
when you break a diamond and
many little pieces remain each like a
diamond chip although they stand out
proof
in the class so I saw that the phoenix
and the in the second test of this class that
we are not going to finish is with its
error abdomen is called
diamond chips in Tibet in Tibetan because being
Dorian could be 'tories' the why
dreaming because it means give me diamond
and 2006 with Jennings King James Kingston
and 22 means jewel which means king or
lord just because therefore he is the king
of gems since he is the king of
gems of stones begins
windbreak sandinism feet life and baker
glass sec more means when you break
something each little piece as if you break a
glass
walking davis leavers and you tell everyone
friends musiak be careful walking here
because there are many sharp chips and pieces
that  Take out prüfer you keep the
second proof of emptiness that we're going
to talk about
is the diamond chip to Taiwan
number 3
tell me that I have I have a month and
in the 55
[Music]
to Yan Jiangying also must a
young girl approached during the
break
Sam's smart love will they give or not some
smart mom or dad
West Sitting article this report have been
explained inter baum then I
was teaching her how to grow little plants
I have dug mental seeds
what's it called
well she
came with me and she was very proud it was
like a container in that shot
walk and a sprout came out I
bring here to world skies nothing and she said
look I that this harvest is made of
yingxiu and this is another teaching of another
skill of today to teach
except gateways is
accept the gift with fats that live
action mine in your mind in fact
if you're not thinking how the hell am I going to
put these animals to add value in
this I'm going to have soil giving away from
the suitcase
but you say there's thank you very much
and he says
in fact they will be it's not a gift anything
more than  I was teaching her to
think, I held on for 90
[Music]
and now suddenly I want to
keep her, I don't know what happened and she tells me,
go ahead, LG, she
gave it a good one
and I said, don't you want to give it to me and they say
no because we're talking about this
before the sprawl theme before the
sprout emerges, Walter
Inning in the Park, there
was something in the pot or not,
like
if you can say it continues alone, there was a
seed in the water and then you put
water where they worry and the seeds
open in the next month
[Music] little
plant, the sprout emerges from Carlet
Bergua sed wasser ex Miguel of water ex
Miguel or directly
in the Catholic Church they ask, but
then we demand
that, did that arise from nothing
in the Scan Station channel and vacation and
you can have this conversation about
the creation of Western Bit Brain, what is
the direct debate, dissatisfied
Nate, did everything arise from nothing,
Western Nothing in the Park, the Western
Santander of youth writes
in this container,
from nothing did
the sprout grow or from something that the
sprout arose, shops
[Music]
camping or spray with nothing, did the
sprout grow from nothing or did the
sprout grow from the 'guaje'? Observe
Emery New Main, I'm reading your mind
and now I have to say that they're thinking
that it's chopped in Flanders, Tim Redding,
of course it came from the seed, in fact,
although in France, before seeing if it came
from something that was already there and traveling, well, they have
us in a... have to take... if
you have a container that doesn't have a
seed then nothing is going to sprout, they're
birds, so obviously, if I've done it, it's if you
give me an option, which
will... let's see which of the two is correct, they tend to...
dum girls is the one that most... and
then the girl's sprout
comes from a seed or directly... ex... miss
love and lasting... or it comes from... I
have to say then that they're
thinking that it's the bed... anyway, they're
thinking that the... we come
from the seed and... fan of Buddha, if I am the
Buddha, even post-crisis... I would
say both answers are wrong... of
sprout, they have with... from that... in the... the
sprout didn't come from nothing
and then they have camps, they have... and the
sprout didn't come from...  something
[Music]
you'll have to walk have extinguished
daily life I'm not going to explain it in detail
but it's James's idea as
goals are scored life with my first in my
mind westlife
well he
perhaps things come from something else like
when my teacher told me that the mind
is like a very big and long 'spaghetti
western' acting nataine nat in which they
live
or then the other option is that there was
nothing there was nobody there was nothing
and suddenly big band with me which of
the two hardness is correct according to him
no street in this web nest none and
soft string it's very frustrating to talk aid
to work for women will expand America
I'm glad I don't work for him and I'm
glad I'm not married to him
ok
[Music]
moix and king of music it's not that I don't have
a ford prove argentinas de we are going to
study in class member ex 49
four
class tests entín is test number 4 of
emptiness that emery
[Music]
counts of the cross is the theme
when the girl's sprout emerges
and there are four others  options we can
have from groups for choice in their
people there is
a group of four forces that
we can not very good number one
[Music]
who
exa
the sprout emerged from itself from spray
grau
the sprout emerged from the sprout
ok which is impossible
we have to review every possibility
[Music]
wow did
that sprout emerge from itself
tristan bauer option number one word or
sadly option number 263 proud
wolf opinion did that sprout grow from
something else as well as a seed of
singers is the second with its
devils understand of the turned the
choose still listen that all the
others
behind spray camps have sanping which
is combination habits of in santiago or
did that sprout emerge from something that is a
combination of itself and something more
serious is that is number three fourth is
option 4
[Music]
even is cam band teen did the sprout
emerge from that nothing to do and that I
repeat for choice is four options of
when you connect when you teach it
you can do so
formed by 0 dollars
dave stewart now everyone already  They're like
Quique, that's why it
's at 0.2.
There are four options.
Number one, himself,
in that the outbreak was already there a
year ago and then emerged today in parents of
drivers and in skill discs, and by the way, there are
schools in India that
believe this. Here,
Sankan, the children's home, like
Tanzania, the
main yoga school, that they take out
choice. Second option, spray came from,
also the flag, so the outbreak emerged from
something else, like a seed. Third
option, and after I got sick, if they think they
have the Bronx, there's Santander
in option number 3, the outbreak emerged from
something else, from himself. Ward Sears, option
number 4, and Canfranc Nate emerged from nothing, out of
nowhere, although which way news, which would
I choose?
And 23 in English, they have a saying, a
way of saying things, which is none
of the above.
[Music]
It's test number 4, that with the
mold, Volstad in Whittier, Infinite Picas,
travel, Te Des Castell, in that means William and Tennis
World Water, and that
means Guanábana de Richter,
what.
[Applause]
So we're going to stop here.
After the last one, and that's because it
means we had to analyze the
best, and that means we have
pending things, and that means we're going to have to
review it again, and that
means we're going to have to have
another retreat. That the Charles Line MGF
[Applause]
is everyone who was going to check
out at 12, it's extended until 12.
Those who were going to the airport at 12,
now it's going to be at 12:30. Your
current everybody Google and Bing, now you
are living the current series
in the boyfriend of seats on this date.
[Music]
The Special Case and New Line and
Wasserstein's Living After, and if you have to
catch a plane, the transport is going to
leave at 12:30, and this line
tour
here, so
[Music]
AVN, you have widgets, name the deep end in
my name, it's
called the test of emptiness, which is
called or named
dependent origination, okay,
admission saints
and Scott respectively,
term Rick Veitch, it
's not a mere FARC, Scott the king of
kings, and in express, sometimes the
number test  5 is called will have the one that
Rick stops
and means
the king of the tests there is no
better it is the highest of all the
tests
[Music]
know mind I have seven minutes left and I
keep deport they want to go deeper
nothing to reach aliens
efe
[Music]
city the three in this last reason of
which the king of all reasons 16
mtv that extend by law and that
is empty because it is
independent origination of hard with the fame
interpretations there are three
different interpretations in it is it with your
heart banier planning and your
body shop coming tour and it's good to
have them in you in your
toolbox of the bodhisattva wind ivicam
chichester when you become a master
or mistress sambar is life'
as if everyone is having
fights almost divorce with their husbands
at the kings
white where today the artist signs
track and you tell him no wait don't do it again anyway
something to fix in my
van I can fix it by force
and next min
no divorce for next week
first time we choose first we have to
try to use my three tools and f
word  Let's see if
this teaser works, by the way, when you're
a jazz acy teacher at a classical
institute, it
's one of the most common questions they're going to ask you,
and this is what I used to really want,
my boyfriend didn't attend, Kings and State,
explore, and yesterday, well, I was already thinking
that we should cut the world, the
best thing, and I thought, and one of the best
things you can do isn't fat or two
clear ones, and no, no, no,
look, you just have to go to
Alesha Dixon's class, which is going to be in two
weeks, it
depends on you,
and just ask her about the three
tests of dependent origination
that serve as a test for emptiness,
so, WikiLeaks words, and I think
that's going to help you, why don't you get divorced?
The wait for two weeks, so they're going to
wait for two weeks, directly in
Malawi, explain Iraq, Lebanon, and then it doesn't
matter if you explain it correctly or
not, this dude, Twister, Steny Hoyer, and if they
wait two more weeks, their
anger is over anyway, although this
weekend, just in case, for two weeks, if they
wait two weeks and spend it
eating cupcakes for two weeks
Christian won that Timur anyway they're
not going to get away with a banquet because you're
not going to get divorced show the
sampling delay delays a Phoenix this
problem ok if something delays many times just
delaying the situation fixed
my member's problem of cheering
then they remember that if they're
turned on
the mind
[Music]
flower party dependent on nation
advice been lady with fire winter jasmine
and making this is the advice of  The
lower part of the middle path school for
the woman who has fights with the
lower shield will depend on nation advice.
The lower part's advice regarding
dependent origination is
no longer Halloween,
and if not, well, he's yelling at me all the
time, and I said, look, you can use
emptiness on WhatsApp. It has to be what is
emptiness in Tim Smith's ex-law of Zion,
Wildcats for one, and SAP set. Emptiness
means that there is actually a
real cause for why he's angry.
There's no one in the kitchen, Google
apps for no Ruiz Cano. There is no
husband in the kitchen who is angry for no
reason.
Download and planning nation, a very, very
low dependent origination. He didn't tell me,
and blood, look, he was probably
hungry. Stein told me, maybe he was tired.
I told myself,
firework, maybe he had a fight with someone
at work,
erviti on duty. Everything has a cause,
a reason, right?
And the husband who gets angry for no
reason doesn't exist. That's emptiness, okay?
That's the lowest explanation, and
textile depends on me. It's still
interdependent origination. The golden
heart, let's go now a little higher.
In schools
far from that, there was
swelling
[Music]
by Max Layton and also, but in fact, you don't have to be
mad at me.
There are many parts in the Georgia Focus and
winning in Haiti, but you're just
focusing on the negative parts. Fixed
on Lavin and Sky with the Kids, he has
some very good parts. He's very
loving with the children.
Iger Spears and After and Harris have
very good hugs. Once you know, they
have no idea. Awards, there are good things. There are good
parts. It's Nobody One Park. It's not just one
part. Jimenez of
filtering, this is him. It's many parts
together. Or what? Wang bringing that first, let's
say, one part is a problem, and 10 in
Greg get mad that for America, but
look at all the good parts. Sign up,
Children, he's good with the children. Works,
Gardens with Sam, he works very hard, he has a
good salary in late night,
and then later at night, you know there are
good things.
That's part 2 of the
interdependent origination. Fresh, they depend on
their parts. First level of learning things,
he depends on his causes, and this is the
Beat is just hungry, style is
tired, daughter of Trouble the World, had
problems at work, babies, type in
Miss Mexico, is the
lowest dependent origination, to release a little higher, well, you have to
recognize that he has
some good things, not gray and they are the same
as nobody, only one thing, daughters,
discourse conditions, he also has these
good qualities of someone who is good with
children and Imex and yes, well, FM, the support of
the family, although this way
always has a difficult temperament
[Music]
but there is more and that's like half, it's
like a level that is now,
we will finish with the mass of Mitsui's wifi
and with this we finish the relay
and it is very lucky to finish with the
highest explanation
and I still owe you an explanation of
Kim's other additions, but this is
the king
and here we go,
well
[Music]
we helped 10,
mine is that in question
I am Spanish and free, so the tea has been
screaming, right?
Yes, I'm
going to ask you something, Mallorcan, had
some children
[Music]
maybe, maybe, he was a New Yorker when you
scream at children, suicide, it
puts a seed in your mind in  The next
week and the following week I sing of
caching in which you go to Ciro's kitchen
the seeds open in me
[Music]
a long way
and maybe everyone in the world gets
exactly what they deserve
maybe this one Javier present justice
in the way maybe there is a
100% nomadic justice maybe the universe is
100% fair my life
Albers that I maybe those who
shout receive shouts what stands out
is